Moore, Frank C.; Papers apap223
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- State Association of Towns, 1881-1949; 1
  - Pamphlet File, 1881-1949; 1.2; 0.9 cubic ft.
    - #50.Part One of the Report of the New York State Commission for the Revision of the Tax Laws, 1932 (Box 2 (1-State Association of Towns), Folder 42)
    - #51.Depression Taxes and Economy Through Reform of Local Government: Third Report of the New York State Commission for the Revision of the Tax Laws, 1933 (Box 2 (1-State Association of Towns), Folder 43)
    - #93. New York State Special Joint Committee on Taxation and Retrenchment Fiscal Problems of City School Administration: A Report, 1928 (Box 2 (1-State Association of Towns), Folder 44)
    - #94. New York State Special Joint Committee on Taxation and Retrenchment Construction of School Buildings in the Towns and Smaller Cities of New York, 1929 (Box 2 (1-State Association of Towns), Folder 45)
    - #96. New York State Special Joint Committee on Taxation and Retrenchment, Report, 1925 (Box 2 (1-State Association of Towns), Folder 46)
    - #99. New York State Special Joint Committee on Taxation and Retrenchment Tax Exemption in State of New York: A Preliminary Report, 1927 (Box 2 (1-State Association of Towns), Folder 47)
    - New York State Special Joint Committee on Taxation and Retrenchment, Report, 1924 (Box 2 (1-State Association of Towns), Folder 48)
    - New York State Special Joint Committee on Taxation and Retrenchment, Report, 1922 (Box 2 (1-State Association of Towns), Folder 49)
- New York State Comptroller, 1941-1950; 2; 2 cubic ft.
  This series contains records related to Frank Moore's service as New York State Comptroller. It includes an extensive file of news clippings on Moore's unsuccessful 1941 campaign and successful 1942 campaign for the office, as well as correspondence, memoranda and publications. Of particular note is a folder of material related to the investigation of the Albany political machine.
  - 1941 Campaign for State Comptroller (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 1)
  - 1942 Campaign for State Comptroller (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 2)
  - 1942 Campaign for State Comptroller - Cole, Seth T. (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 3)
  - 1942 Campaign - Advertisements and Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 4-5)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings, 1942 June (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 6)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings, 1942 July (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 7)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings, 1942 August (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 8)
  - 150th Anniversary of Comptroller's Office, 1947 (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 9)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings, 1942 August; 5 folders (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 10-14)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings, 1942 September; 2 folders (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 15-16)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings (Folders 1-2 of 4), 1942 October; 2 folders (Box 3 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 17-18)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings (Folders 3-4 of 4), 1942 October; 2 folders (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 1-2)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings, 1942 November (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 3)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings, 1942 December (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 4)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings - Special (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 5)
  - 1942 Campaign - News Clippings - Specials & Editorials (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 6)
  - Albany Investigation (O'Brien, Haner and Delaney), 1943-1944 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 7)
  - Campaign Leaflets, 1946 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 9)
  - Election Returns, 1942-1950 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 10)
  - Federal - State - Local Fact Sheet for Each State (Binder), Undated (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 11)
  - Field Day and Clam Steam, 1945-1946 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 12)
  - Handbook of Public Assistance Administration, 1949; 2 folders (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 13-14)
  - Hanley, Joe. R., 1943- 1950 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 15)
  - Justices and Magistrates Association, 1950 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 16)
  - Letters and Clippings Re: Statement not to Seek Renomination as State Comptroller, 1950 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 17)
  - Memoranda, 1947-1948 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 18)
  - New York City Fiscal Program, 1946 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 19)
  - New York State/ New York City Fiscal Data, 1945-1947 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 20)
  - Political Campaigns, 1942-1950 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 21)
  - Publications, 1943-1945 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 22)
  - School of Government Proposal, 1943 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 23)
  - State & Local Elections, 1943 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 24)
  - Uniform System of Accounts for Counties, 1950 (Box 4 (2-New York State Comptroller), Folder 25)
- New York State Lieutenant Governor, 1948-1954; 3
  This series contains the records of Moore's service as New York State Lieutenant Governor.
  - General Subject File, 1948-1954; 3.1; 3 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains a range of subject files which document Moore's activities as Lieutenant Governor. They are arranged alphabetically by subject and include the records of Moore's 1950 campaign for the office, materials related to various studies conducted by the Lieutenant Governor's Office, an extensive file of correspondence related to Moore's 1953 resignation from office, and numerous files on individual subjects.
    - 1950 Campaign - Balch, Richard (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 1)
    - 1950 Campaign - Contributions (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 2)
    - 1950 Campaign - Correspondence (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 3)
    - 1950 Campaign - Letters of Congratulation re: Nomination (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 4)
    - 1950 Campaign - Letters Used in Campaign (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 5)
    - 1950 Campaign - Publicity, 2 folders (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 6-7)
    - 1950 Campaign - Republican State Convention (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 8)
    - 1950 Campaign - Voting Machine (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 9)
    - 1950 Campaign - Workers (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 10)
    - Angelus, Dorothy, 1951-1953 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 11)
    - Association of Towns, 1953 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 12)
    - Audit and Control, 1948 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 13)
    - "Big Six" Cities, 1951 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 14)
    - Black River Regulating District, 1950 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 15)
    - Bond Sales - Rules and Regulations of State Comptroller, 1951 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 16)
    - Bronx Park Community Project, 1951 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 17)
    - Business Taxes, 1952-1953 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 18)
    - Census - Federal, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 19)
    - Certiorari, 1951 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 20)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1952 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 21)
    - City of Buffalo, 1951 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 22)
    - City of Lackawanna, 1952 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 23)
    - City of Rochester, 1952-1953 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 24)
    - City of Schenectady, 1952 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 25)
    - City of Yonkers, 1953 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 26)
    - Cities, Towns, and Villages in New York State by Country, Undated (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 27)
    - Citizens' Budget Commission, Inc., 1951 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 28)
    - Civil Defense, 1951 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 29)
    - Clippings, Miscellaneous, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 30)
    - Committee of Supervisory Groups Survey, 1951 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 31)
    - Conference of Mayors, 1951-1953 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 32)
    - Constitutional Amendments, 1951-1953 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 33)
    - Constitutional Debt Limit Amendment, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 35)
    - County Economic Statistics, 1953 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 36)
    - Defense Spending Retrenchment Survey, 1953 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 37)
    - Education Aid - Measure of Ability, 1952 (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 38)
    - Education Aid Study (Folders 1-2 of 3), 1952; 2 folders (Box 5 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 39-40)
    - Education Aid Study (Folder 3 of 3), 1952 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 1)
    - Education Finance Study, 1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 2)
    - Eldred, Dr. Arvie, 1950-1954 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 3)
    - Estimates and "Trial Tables", 1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 4)
    - F - Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 5)
    - H - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 6)
    - Handbook of Public Assistance Administration, Part 5 (Binder), 1951 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 7)
    - Hayes, Frederick O., 1950-1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 8)
    - Index Card File, 1951-1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 9)
    - J - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 10)
    - Joint Rules of Senate and Assembly, (1831), 1952 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 11)
    - Letters re: Resignation as Lieutenant Governor, A - G, 1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 12)
    - Letters re: Resignation as Lieutenant Governor, H - M, 1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 13)
    - Letters re: Resignation as Lieutenant Governor, M - O, 1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 14)
    - Letters re: Resignation as Lieutenant Governor, O - S, 1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 15)
    - Letters re: Resignation as Lieutenant Governor, S - Y, 1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 16)
    - Letters re: Resignation as Lieutenant Governor, Accretion, 1953; 2 folders (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 17-18)
    - Local Fiscal Resources, 1951-1952 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 19)
    - Management Survey, 1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 20)
    - McGovern, J. Raymond, 1950-1952 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 21)
    - New York City Budget, 1952-1953 (Box 6 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 22)
    - New York City Fiscal Program, 1953; 3 folders (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 1-3)
    - New York City Fiscal Program - Plan and Comments, 1953 (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 4)
    - New York State Bar Association, 1950-1951 (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 5)
    - Parking, 1952 (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 6)
    - Possible Revenue Sources, 1952-1953 (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 7)
    - Reallocation of Tax Sources, 1953 (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 8)
    - School Buildings Legislation, 1952-1953 (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 9)
    - School Economics Study, 1951-1953 (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 10)
    - State Aid, 1950-1953; 7 folders (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 11-17)
    - Value of Taxable Farm Real Estate in New York State, Undated (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 18)
    - Welfare, Federal Aid to New York State (Settlement of Old Claims), 1954 (Box 7 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 19)
  - Welfare Project, 1948-1954; 3.2; 1 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains material related to the Lieutenant Governor's Office's study of the public welfare system. Organized alphabetically by subject, it includes reports, publications, correspondence, and a variety of individual subject files.
    - "Across - the - Board" Reimbursement, 1949 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 1)
    - Assignments, 1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 2)
    - Audit & Control, 1950-1951 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 3)
    - Broome County, 1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 4)
    - Children's Court Matter, 1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1951-1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 7)
    - Day Care, 1952 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 8)
    - Federal Aid, 1952 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 9)
    - Governor's Messages, 1948-1951; 1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 10)
    - Hamilton County, 1949 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 11)
    - History of Public Welfare in New York State by Dr. Schneider, Undated (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 12)
    - Home Relief, 1952-1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 13)
    - Hospitalization, 1952 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 14)
    - Hospital Rates, 1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 15)
    - Lansdale, Robert T., 1953-1954 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 16)
    - Meetings, 1952-1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 17)
    - Memoranda, 1951-1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1951-1952 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 19)
    - Net Effect of Proposed Revisions in State Aid, Undated (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 20)
    - New York City, 1952 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 21)
    - Problems Involved - Functions Other than Public Assistance, Undated (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 22)
    - Public Assistance, 1951 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 23)
    - Publications, 1951-1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 24)
    - Releases, 1952-1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 25)
    - Report - The Home Relief Story (New York State Department of Social Welfare), 1950 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 26)
    - Report - Lutz Report, 1951 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 27)
    - Report - New York State Department of Social Welfare, 12/18/1950 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 28)
    - Report on Social Welfare - California, 1952 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 29)
    - Report - Temporary Commission Welfare Study, 1952 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 30)
    - Schools - Welfare and Service Officers, 1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 31)
    - Senator Wise, 1951 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 32)
    - State Aid - Tuberculosis, [1953?] (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 33)
    - State Aid - Types of, 1951-1952 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 34)
    - State Aid - Welfare by County, 1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 35)
    - State Aid Formula - New York State Department of Social Welfare, Undated (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 36)
    - State Aid Formulae - Welfare and TB, 1952-1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 37)
    - Tax Rates & Tax Margins, 1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 38)
    - Welfare Study Outline, 1953 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 39)
    - W.J. Embler, 1950-1951 (Box 8 (3-New York State Lieutenant Governor), Folder 40)
- New York State Constitution, 1937-1968; 4
  This series contains records relating to the revision of the New York State Constitution.
  - 1938 Constitutional Convention, 1937-1939; 4.1; 0.75 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains material on the 1938 New York State Constitutional Convention, at which Moore served as Chairman of the Committee on Villages. It includes the records of the Committee on Villages and extensive files of pamphlets and newspaper clippings. This subseries is organized alphabetically by subject.
    - 1915 Constitutional Convention - Publications of the New York State Constitution Convention Commission of 1914-1915 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 1)
    - 1915 Constitutional Convention - Pamphlets (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1937 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 3)
    - Committee on Villages, 1938; 2 folders (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 4-5)
    - Constitutional Conventions, 1938 and prior (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 6)
      Miscellaneous Data.
    - Convention Ticket, 1938 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 7)
    - General, 1937-1938 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Material, 1938 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 9)
    - News Clippings on 1938 Constitutional Convention (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 10)
    - News Clippings on 1938 Constitutional Convention (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 11)
    - News Clippings on 1938 Constitutional Convention (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 12)
    - News Clippings on 1938 Constitutional Convention (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 13)
    - News Clippings on 1938 Constitutional Convention (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 14)
    - Pamphlets and Printed Matter, 1937-1938 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 15)
    - Pamphlets and Printed Matter, 1937-1939 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 16)
    - Resolutions, 1938 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 17)
  - Temporary State Commission on the 1959 Constitutional Convention / Special Legislative Committee on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution, 1955-1960; 4.2; 1.75 cubic ft.
    This subseries contains material on the Temporary State Commission on the 1959 Constitutional Convention and its successor the Special Legislative Committee on the Revision and Simplification of the Constitution. It consists primarily of internal background studies prepared for Commission staff on a variety of subjects related to New York State government, including studies of the municipal government of several metropolitan areas. It also contains a number of files on individual subjects. It is organized alphabetically by subject.
    - Alaska Constitutional Convention, 1956 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 18)
    - Amendments to the Constitution, 1955 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 19)
    - Background Studies - Apportionment of the Legislature, 1960 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 20)
    - Background Studies - Civil Service, Public Officers, and Retirement - Retirement, 1958 (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 21)
    - Background Studies - Local Government - Metropolitan Binghamton, 1958; 2 folders (Box 9 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 22-23)
    - Background Studies - Local Government - Metropolitan Elmira, 1958; 2 folders (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 1-2)
    - Background Studies - Local Government - Metropolitan Poughkeepsie, 1958; 2 folders (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 3-4)
    - Background Studies - Local Government - Metropolitan Syracuse, First Draft, 1957 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 5)
    - Background Studies - Local Government - Metropolitan Syracuse, 1958; 2 folders (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 6-7)
    - Background Studies - Local Government - Metropolitan Utica - Rome, 1958; 2 folders (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 8-9)
    - Background Studies - Natural Resources and Economic Development - Canals, 1960 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 10)
    - Background Studies - Natural Resources and Economic Development - Housing and Urban Renewal, 1959 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 11)
    - Background Studies - Suffrage and Elections, 1959 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 12)
    - Background Studies - Taxation and Finance - Auditing, Accounting and Management of Funds, 1958 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 13)
    - Background Studies - Taxation and Finance - Highway Finance, 1958 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 14)
    - Background Studies - Taxation and Finance - Real Property Assessment, 1959 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 15)
    - Background Studies - Taxation and Finance - Tax Exemptions, 1959 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 16)
    - Biographies - Various, 1959 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 17)
    - Clippings, 1955-1957 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 18)
    - Clippings, 1957-1958 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 19)
    - Hearings - Albany, 1957 June 05 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 20)
    - Hearings - New York City, 1957 June 14 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 21)
    - Hinman, George, 1956-1957 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 22)
    - Inter - Law School Committee, 1957 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 23)
    - Laws of 1956, Chapter 814 - Creation of Temporary State Commission (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 24)
    - Members, 1956 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 25)
    - Notes and Memoranda, 1956 (Box 10 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 26)
    - Pamphlet, 1956-1957 (Box 11 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 2)
    - Pending Amendments to the Constitution and Pending Propositions, 1958 (Box 11 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 3)
    - Research Studies, 1956-1958 (Box 11 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A.: Copies of Correspondence from the Office of Mr. Rockefeller, 1956-1957 (Box 11 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 5)
    - Ronan, Dr. William J., 1957 (Box 11 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 6)
    - Saxe, Hon. Martin, 1957 (Box 11 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 7)
    - Staff, 1956 (Box 11 (4-New York State Constitution), Folder 8)